HUNTER GILLMAN

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Who I am

My name is Hunter Gillman, and luckily have discovered that my passion is photography. I have successfully operated/created Hunter Gillman Photography from day one of using a camera, to now doing this craft for over six years. (Lightroom/Photoshop) and other photo editing software, in order to perfect and enhance my work. I am a hard working, positive individual constantly in the pursuit of expressive and beautiful shots. I have worked in the retail world for 4+ years and have constantly been able to satisfy customers with great service, but also making wonderful lasting connections with loyal clients in their shopping and overall experience. I would love the opportunity to share my skills and expertise with your company.

WORK HISTORY

Head Photographer/Business Owner, 01/2015 - Current Hunter Gillman Photography, Salt Lake City, UT

- Professional Models and Brand Names utilize my years of experience and unique touch to create the images and overall aesthetic they desire
- All business operations including my website, marketing, social media analytics, and Ecommerce
- Individual and Business customer service and interactions
- · Location preparation, wardrobe, and time of shoot
- Supported photography and video shoots by helping with equipment setup.
- Took photos from different angles and perspectives to capture perfect images.
- Assisted clients in selecting poses, wardrobe and backgrounds to photograph different looks, concepts and locations.
- Reviewed images and selected best frames to present in client portfolio for purchase.
- Created engaging content for Pinterest, Facebook, and Instagram
- Contributed to mock-ups, email campaigns, and social media content
- Performed market analysis and researched latest trends
- Digitally edited photos to enhance appearance.
- Edited, toned, captioned, and uploaded photographs for publication.
- Photographed high-quality images for various print and digital projects.
- Planned and prepared for on-location and studio shoots.
- Scheduled studio appointments to shoot wide variety of subjects.
- Utilized natural and artificial lighting to capture desired images and maintain quality.

Inside Sales/Technical Support Representative, 02/2023 - 06/2023 Help Cloud, Lindon, UT

Sales motivated tech support to completion of new inquires to loyal customers turning them into members, while working as a team to help & sell as much as possible.

- Proven to work well with a team, meet goals, and provide excellent customer service to inexperienced users of computers. Apple, Microsoft, etc.
- Make 60-100 outbound calls to inside leads where customers submitted tickets & the team and I provide them with a care and direction to

- Provo, UT 84601
- 385-454-4276
- h.gillman@outlook.com
- **Bold Profile**

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

• instagram.com/huntergillman

SKILLS

- Customer Service
- Retail Sales
- Social Media Marketing
- Professional Image Editing/Retouching/Creating
- Adobe Creative (Photoshop, Lightroom)
- Social Media Analytics (Instagram, Facebook Ads)
- WordPress
- Salesforce
- SquareSpace Commerce
- SquareSpace Web Design
- Excel Spreadsheets
- Management
- Follow-Up Calls
- Digital Sales
- Marketing Strategies
- Location Scouting
- Lighting and Angles
- Loss Mitigation
- Account Adjustment

decent malicious software, deeper technical issues.

- Focused on selling product to keep clients protected on the internet, and provided 24/7 tech support to answer questions/concerns/retain customers/ and reach sales goals daily & weekly.
- Contributed to team objectives in fast-paced environment.
- Maintained up-to-date knowledge of available products to best serve customers and maximize sales potential.
- Quoted prices, credit terms and other bid specifications.
- Managed customer service inquiries and complaints for customer satisfaction.
- Managed high levels of call flow and responded to Anti-Virus technical support needs
- Monitored system performance to identify potential issues
- Explained security measures in simple terminology to help users understand malware and phishing threats
- · Answered customers' questions regarding products, prices, and availability.

Retail Sales Manager, 11/2021 - 08/2022 Jcrew Factory, Lehi, UT

- I was responsible for the operation of the sales floor, management of staff, handling of deposits, planning floor sets, and ensuring a smooth/successful business operation
- Oversaw employee performance, corrected problems, and increased efficiency to maintain productivity targets.
- Built relationships with customers and community to establish long-term business growth.
- Coached sales associates in product specifications, sales incentives, and selling techniques, significantly increasing customer satisfaction ratings.
- Offered hands-on assistance to customers, assessing needs, and maintaining current knowledge of consumer preferences.
- Trained team members in successful strategies to meet operational and sales targets.
- Achieved sales goals and service targets by cultivating and securing new customer relationships.
- Resolved problems with high-profile customers to maintain relationships and increase return customer base
- Coached sales associates in product specifications, sales incentives, and selling techniques, significantly increasing customer satisfaction ratings

Jr Collector, 04/2021 - 11/2021 Prestige Financial Services, Draper, UT

- Delivered exceptional customer service on collection calls and maintained calm and professional demeanor.
- Maintained high volume of calls and met demands of busy and productive group.
- Contacted customers to discuss past-due accounts and negotiated payment plans.
- Responded to customer inquiries and provided detailed account information.
- Identified and contacted customers with overdue accounts to address payment status
- Resolved customer disputes and disagreements through professional, calm communication to find mutually beneficial solutions
- Established relationships with customers to encourage payment of delinquent accounts
- · Processed debtor payments and updated accounts to reflect new balance
- Located customers with overdue accounts and solicited payment in compliance with fair debt collection practices
- Analyzed customer financial records to determine appropriate payment plan

Keyholder/ Salesman, 01/2018 - 04/2021

J Crew Factory

 As the keyholder and salesman for J Crew Factory I was responsible for closing the store, opening the store, and also making sure that everything ran smoothly while keeping a sales quota and managing other team members

- · Counted out cash drawers and balanced totals.
- Completed store opening and closing procedures.
- Processed cash, credit, debit, and check payments.
- Kept store clean and organized to provide shoppers with pleasant experience.
- Offered hands-on assistance to customers, assessing needs, and maintaining current knowledge of consumer preferences.
- Opened and closed store 5 days per week by counting registers, making deposits, and storing and filing all daily paperwork.

EDUCATION

Degree, English, 2016 Pleasant Grove High - Pleasant Grove, UT

- Honoree of [Honor Name]
- Professional Development: [Subject]
- [Number] GPA 3.8

REFERENCES

REFERENCES:

Store Director at JCrew Factory Chelsey Risher 801.787.1249

Located in: Outlets at Traverse Mountain

Address: 3700 Cabela's Blvd #258, Lehi, UT 84043

Sally Francom Copperlight Communications/Lehi Free Press 801.560.6710

Shane Van Ball STAYWEAR Apparel & Mental Health Brand 208.521.5570